[
  {
    "question": "Launch of sputnik",
    "answer": "1957"
  },
  {
    "question": "(D)ARPA creation",
    "answer": "1958"
  },
  {
    "question": "Message switching introduced",
    "answer": "1963",
    "author": "Leonard Kleinrock"
  },
  {
    "question": "Message blocks introduced",
    "answer": "1964",
    "author": "Paul Baran"
  },
  {
    "question": "Term “Packet” invention",
    "answer": "1965-66",
    "author": "Donald Davies"
  },
  {
    "question": "ARPANET planning begins",
    "answer": "1966",
    "author": "Joseph Licklider (IPTO)"
  },
  {
    "question": "ARPANET development begins",
    "answer": "1967",
    "author": "Larry Roberts (IPTO)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who suggested the use of IMPs and when",
    "answer": "1967",
    "author": "Wesley Clark"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mother of all Demos",
    "answer": "1968",
    "author": "Douglas Engelbart"
  },
  {
    "question": "First Internet connection using IMPs",
    "answer": "1969",
    "author": "L. Kleinrock (UCLI) + D. Engelbart (SRI)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invention of RFCs",
    "answer": "1969",
    "author": "Steve Crocker"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invention of B",
    "answer": "1969",
    "author": "Ken Thompson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invention of C",
    "answer": "1969",
    "author": "Dennis Ritchie"
  },
  {
    "question": "First ARPANET email & Invention of @",
    "answer": "1971",
    "author": "Ray Tomlinson"
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP/IP specified",
    "answer": "1974",
    "author": "Vinton Cerf + Bob Kahn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix integrates IMP (Unix == ARPANET)",
    "answer": "1975"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great Controversy (OSI / ISO)",
    "answer": "1977"
  },
  {
    "question": "SMTP",
    "answer": "1982"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sendmail",
    "answer": "1982",
    "author": "Eric Allman"
  },
  {
    "question": "The great switch",
    "answer": "1983"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unix Wars (BSD vs System V)",
    "answer": "1983"
  },
  {
    "question": "DNS specified",
    "answer": "1984",
    "author": "Paul Mockapetris"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invention of IRC",
    "answer": "1988",
    "author": "Jarkko Oikarinen"
  },
  {
    "question": "First Unix release free of all AT&T licenses",
    "answer": "1988",
    "author": "Unix Tahoe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Invention of the WWW",
    "answer": "1990-92",
    "author": "Tim Berners-Lee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gopher (WWW alternative) released",
    "answer": "1991"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mosaic browser released",
    "answer": "1993"
  },
  {
    "question": "Linux 1.0 released",
    "answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "question": "W3C founded",
    "answer": "1994"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Death of the net\"",
    "answer": "1995"
  },
  {
    "question": "XMPP specified",
    "answer": "1999"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dot-com bubble",
    "answer": "2000"
  }
]